REZA MALEK

Las Vegas, NV · (949)667-8888 · rezmalek7@gmail.com

LinkedIn · Portfolio

I am a highly motivated and dependable Front End Developer with a stellar customer service record and superb work ethic. I have professional experience working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and React. I am a life-long learner and would like to have the opportunity to grow my skills and gain new experiences while contributing to team success.

EXPERIENCE

JUL 2018 - JUN 2020

FRONT END DEVELOPER, Meyab.com

- Maintained and updated HTML, CSS, and JavaScript templates on regular basis and as required.
- Collaborated with colleagues to plan and implement features to improve UI/UX of our website.
- Implemented unit testing to ensure all parts of the codes work properly.
- Used SEO best practices to elevate company's web presence; achieved top 10 Google rankings on several highly competitive keywords.

SEP 2015 - MAY 2020

PHOTOGRAPHER/WEB DEVELOPER, Livia Photo

- Produced compelling photographs for clients including real estate agencies, interior designers, and advertisers.
- Oversaw all aspects of business management including financial, marketing, and customer service.
- Built responsive property websites for realtors to showcase their properties.
- Established authentic relationship with clients, leading to a customer base of 95% repeat business...

JAN 2013 - AUG 2015

MARKETING COORDINATOR, PMC TV

- Assisted in the development and implementation of clients' advertising campaigns.
- Managed social media presence and directed campaigns to improve social media reputation and recognition, resulting in 1.5 million followers.
- Provided market research, forecasts, competitive analyses, campaign results, and consumer trends.

EDUCATION

SEP 2005 – JUN 2009

BACHELOR OF ART IN PHOTOGRAPHY, Tehran Art & Architecture University

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap, SCSS, React
- ECMAScript 6+

- Adobe Photoshop
- Communication
- Teamwork and Collaboration